[The Wolf]
[Episode 26]
Ma Jing, I know you're worried that
Zhai Xing might be sad,
but she needs to
know the truth.
Castellan!
Sorry for my incompetency!
General!
Brother!
Wolfie,
I hope every couple in the world
ends up like us.
I hope they can be honest
with each other.
And have their happily ever after.
Xing Er,
time to sleep.
Carry me back then.
Okay, I'll carry you back.
Ma Zhai Xing,
see you on the battlefield.
[It's time for me]
[to pay with my life.]
Ma Troop, listen up!
General Ma Feng Cheng
had passed away!
Stop!
Why are you sneaking around?
He must be Chu Kui's spy!
He's trying to
report General Ma's passing to them.
Get down!
You!
What else did you tell them?
You guys will never win!
Tell us!
Did you tell them that
Ma Troop knew the truth
about the murder of Ma family?
This...
What should we do?
Maybe he has told them
about General Ma's attempt to rebel.
If Chu Kui knows about this,
he will stop Zhai Xing from coming.
But they need at least one day
before they can receive
the pigeon's letter.
I think Zhai Xing
still has time to leave.
It's just that
we must be quick.
We need to meet her before anyone else.
Princess,
time to depart.
Strange.
Why isn't His Highness sending me off?
Princess,
Lord Bo
was summoned by His Majesty
this morning.
That's why he couldn't send you off.
Tell Lord Bo to
wait for my return.
Princess,
have a safe trip.
Please take care of yourself.
You guys take care as well.
I'll leave now.
Princess.
Master,
Princess has departed.
From this moment onwards,
Ma Zhai Xing and I
will go on our separate ways.
Our ties are severed.
If we meet on the battlefield,
we'll see if Ma Zhai Xing
was blessed by the heavens.
Yes, Lord Bo.
Enter the palace.
Ma Jing,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
If I can't confirm
Princess's safety personally,
I won't be able to face my dead brother.
Fine.
The imperial army can reach
the Ma Troop's camp in many ways.
We'll split up into three groups.
You two,
follow Ma Jing
and search in the north.
The other two should
take the mountain path.
I'll take the main path.
Send us a smoke signal
if you find anything!
-Yes!
Master, what's wrong?
How's the progress?
Ma Zhai Xing is on her way now.
I've investigated the path she's using.
My men are following her as well.
We'll poison her
when we have the chance.
You mustn't fail.
Yes, Master.
It's you?
The antidote!
You're trying to poison Zhai Xing
behind His Majesty's back.
Do you think
His Majesty will release you?
I'll tell His Majesty
about your misdeed right away.
Damn it!
Your Majesty.
Father.
Lord Bo,
you...
You came at the right time!
The spy I planted in Ma Troop
sent us news.
He said Ma Troop
had found new evidence
and they knew that I was the one
who ordered
the assassination of Ma Ying!
They intend to stage a revolt.
But...
But this is strange.
Why aren't they moving
when they're trying to
stage a revolt?
I'm sure
they're waiting for
Ma Zhai Xing to arrive
before they act.
Capture Ma Zhai Xing immediately.
Father,
I just came back from Yao Ji's cell.
Yao Ji ordered her men
to poison Ma Zhai Xing on her way there.
Ma Zhai Xing must be safe!
She's my hostage now!
I need her to stay alive!
Bring Night Fury
and stop Ma Zhai Xing immediately!
Bring her back!
Yes, Father.
Let's take a break.
We'll go to Taibao Battalion later.
Sir, what would you like?
Give me the best tea.
And some snacks.
Sure, please have a seat.
Please have a seat.
Sit down.
Yes, Princess.
Is there no one
willing to sit with me?
Princess, we're low-rank troops.
It's unsuitable for us to sit together.
Fine.
I won't force it since you guys
are so disciplined.
Sir,
your snacks.
And your tea.
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
The carriage is ready.
Prepare to depart!
Let's take a look inside.
Yes.
Let's depart!
Miss Ma Jing,
there's no one inside.
Get on the horse!
Ma Jing!
Princess?
Princess!
I've finally found you!
Is it really you?
Were you alone?
Lord Bo sent his men to escort me.
Just now,
I wanted them to stop.
I wanted to see if you were there.
I didn't expect them
to tell me to move along
and not waste any time.
Do you know this?
I lied to them.
I told them I had a stomachache.
And I asked them to wait for me.
We shouldn't stay here!
Let's leave!
Hurry!
Hurry! Get on my horse!
Wait.
Hurry! Follow me!
Ma Jing, what's going on?
I'll tell you everything
when we're safe.
Ma Jing,
what exactly is going on?
Princess,
you must be prepared for the news
that I'm going to tell you right now.
Ma Jing,
why are you wearing this attire?
Don't tell me...
My brother...
He had passed away.
Ma Jing,
let's return to Ma Troop's camp.
I want to send Brother Feng Cheng off.
Stop!
Surround them!
Princess Ma,
you're not allowed to leave.
You guys misunderstood us!
Ma Jing is my family!
Princess,
I'm sure Lord Bo
sent them to kill us.
What are you saying?
Why is Lord Bo trying to kill us?
Kill Ma Zhai Xing!
Stop!
Leave Ma Zhai Xing alive.
His Majesty has an order.
Bring her back to the Imperial City.
Who are you?
Arrest her!
Why are they following your orders?
No.
They aren't Lord Bo's men at all.
They're just impersonating them!
Lord Bo
did send them here!
Because
King of Jin
isn't the one who wiped out your family!
It's Chu Kui
and Lord Bo!
Impossible.
I'm sure Lord Bo isn't the culprit.
Who exactly are you?
Not every woman
can make me care for them.
Even if they're my consorts.
It's all because you're Ma Zhai Xing.
Are you still Wolfie?
I will always be Wolfie in front of you.
Heavens, thank you
for bringing us together.
And make us love each other.
Why?
Under His Majesty's order,
I'm here to arrest the criminal,
Ma Zhai Xing.
Take her away.
Hold it right there!
Princess!
Stop!
-Stop!
-Princess!
Hold it right there!
Ma Zhai Xing,
I will tell you everything
that you want to know.
But do you have the courage
to bear the truth?
Why did you
kill my entire family?
Why did my father do wrong?
He protected the borders
and stayed in the army his entire life.
I'm sure
this is a misunderstanding.
I'm sure you weren't
the one who wiped out my family.
I'm sure it's the King of Jin,
am I right?
The truth is Ma Ying's merits
were too great for his own good.
The truth is
I sent you to the battlefield
because His Majesty wanted to kill you
and the entire Ma Troop.
The truth is
the man you love
is a tool of your father's killer!
As long as I can be with you,
I don't care about anything else.
Even if your love is fake.
If I could pretend,
I hope that
the misdeeds that I've committed
haven't happened at all.
But when you say that
you want a pure relationship
without any lies,
I realized that
I can't do it.
What did he use you for?
A weapon for war.
Princess, you may
know Wolfie well,
but you don't know Lord Bo at all.
When I return to the Court,
I'm not Wolfie anymore.
I'm Lord Bo.
She said
we were cursed by the heavens.
And that we will never be together.
I often think that
it would be better for me
to end my life by jumping off the cliff.
Don't tell me there's an ambush?
What if I were the ambush?
If you and I fight,
it means that Wolfie is dead.
Only Lord Bo is left.
The truth is
Wolfie and Xing Er
will never be together!
The truth is
you and I
were cursed by the heavens!
The truth is
I still hope that
you're lying to me even when
we're in this state!
Arrest Ma Zhai Xing and Ma Jing.
Bring them back to the Capital.
-Yes, my lord.
How dare you
try to poison His Majesty's hostage?
Stay put with your master.
His Majesty has no time for you two now.
You two should reflect on your actions.
And wait for His Majesty's punishment.
Master.
How's the situation?
Do you have any news?
After Ma Troop
knew the truth about
the murder of Ma family,
they tried to stage a revolt.
Ma Zhai Xing was captured by Lord Bo.
Now, she's the hostage of His Majesty.
Lord Bo didn't let her go?
No.
He treats her like a criminal.
Now, they're enemies.
This is their cursed fate
from the start.
The true Lord Bo will awaken soon.
Soon.
The true Lord Bo will return soon.
He will require my assistance.
Seems like we'll be out soon.
It's our brothers from Ma Troop!
Search the front!
-Yes!
What happened?
Princess!
Lord Bo took Princess away!
We were too late.
What are we waiting for?
Attack the Capital
and save Princess!
No!
Now, our forces are weak.
We're no match for Lord Bo.
And we can't save Zhai Xing
and Ma Jing without a plan.
What should we do if Chu Kui
does kill Princess?
Although they've exposed our plan,
Zhai Xing
is still of use to Chu Kui.
As long as Chu Kui
has Ma Zhai Xing in his hand,
the Ma Troop will behave themselves.
Chu Kui
will certainly suppress us
with every chance he gets.
Let's return to our camp
and form a plan.
Return to the camp!
Princess!
Don't touch me.
Let go of me!
I can walk by myself!
Let me out!
You liar! Let me out!
Princess!
Princess treated you guys well,
you know?
How can you guys
be so cruel and unscrupulous?
All of you are worse than dogs!
You're right.
I'm speechless.
Hai Die!
I treated you
as my best friend, you know?
You and Lord Bo,
how could you two be the ones
behind Castellan's death?
How could you guys
do such a cruel thing?
Just treat it as if
you knew the wrong person.
Come back!
Keep watch over them.
I'll report to Master.
Mo Xiao,
I have questions for you.
Princess.
Is Lord Bo really the one
who wiped out my family?
That damned Ma Troop!
One step is all I need
for me to succeed!
But...
But everything went wrong
in the last step!
They even joined the Jin Troop?
This is great!
Jin got our Ma Troop
without any effort!
But you were able to sever your ties
with Ma Zhai Xing
and bring her back to me.
Lord Bo,
I will compensate you
in the future.
Ma Troop
had joined Jin.
The most important thing now
is to use Ma Zhai Xing
to control Ma Troop
so that Jin doesn't dare
to act recklessly.
Ma Troop
is a huge boost to the strength
of Jin Troop.
That King of Jin,
he'll try everything to save
Ma Zhai Xing in order to
gain the favour of Ma Troop.
Lord Bo, ask your guards
to guard over her.
No mistakes are allowed!
Yes.
Ma Zhai Xing is still poisoned.
At this very moment,
she's the most important
hostage we have.
She must be safe.
You're right.
Zhang Jin!
Before I put Yao Ji in jail,
I forced her
to give me the antidote.
I knew
this would happen.
Here.
Go and neutralize the poison
in her body.
Yes, Father.
Master,
Ma Jing and Princess
are in prison now.
This is the antidote.
Put an adequate amount
in her food or water.
And let Ma Zhai Xing consume them.
Remember,
you must keep the poison
a secret from her.
According to her personality,
she won't follow your instructions.
Yes.
Master,
aren't you going to visit her?
She's a hostage and a criminal.
There's no need for me to visit her.
Have some food.
So nice?
Did you poison the food?
I won't commit
such an atrocious act.
Yeah.
You're only good at
slaughtering people in the dark.
Get out!
I don't want to see you!
Eat while it's hot.
Scram!
Close the door.
If you hurt Princess,
I won't let you off
even if I become a ghost!
Princess, time to eat.
I want to see Lord Bo.
Princess,
drink it while it's hot.
Princess!
I want to see Lord Bo!
Did they bully you?
I will prepare a new one for you.
Princess!
I'll say this again.
Bring me to Lord Bo!
Princess, calm down.
Princess,
put down the shard.
I'll bring you to Master.
Here, give me the shard.
I promise I'll bring you
to Master.
I promise.
Princess,
you're no match
for us.
Why are you doing this?
I told you I want to see Lord Bo!
Don't you understand me?
I understand.
I'll report to Master immediately.
She insisted on seeing you.
She even tried to hurt herself.
She was injured by accident
when I try to
snatch away the shard from her.
Is it serious?
Just some minor cuts. Nothing serious.
This is the remaining antidote.
I'll return it to you.
The problem is
Princess
hasn't consumed the food yet.
The poison is still in her body.
Master,
shouldn't you visit
Princess?
Under what identity?
As Wolfie?
Or as Lord Bo who broke her heart?
But...
I will beg Father
to let Ma Zhai Xing go.
And I will trade one life for another.
Master,
how are you going to do that?
I'll let Zhai Xing kill me personally
in order to avenge her family.
This is the best way
for me to atone for my sins.
And it's the best ending
for both of us.
Master!
Hai Die.
Master,
aren't you going to
visit Princess tomorrow?
Let me think about it.
I still have some antidote left.
[Xing Er,]
[I could only neutralize your poison]
[by bringing you back.]
[I will make sure you're safe.]
His Majesty ordered us
to assassinate them!
But he's blaming
Master
for their deaths!
Why is he doing this?
But isn't it the same
if we do
the dirty deeds for Master?
I dare to say this.
I'm sure Master
has always been thinking about this.
Maybe,
he has been thinking about
using his life to atone
for his sins
ever since
he gave Princess
the wolf bow.
Princess!
Why do you look so pale?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Ma Jing, dress her wound.
This...
How did you
get such a big cut on your hand?
Does it hurt?
It doesn't.
Just tell me if you're in pain!
Please don't keep it to yourself!
Silly girl, why are you crying?
My hand doesn't hurt at all.
You're lying!
You're a human!
I'm sure it hurts!
I'm in pain when I look at it!
Princess!
Ma Jing, don't cry.
Don't cry.
According to reports,
Chu Kui built many
underground cells that are
unknown to people.
It's hard for us to identify
the exact cell that Princess is in.
And now, I'm sure Chu Kui
has handed over the defence
to Lord Bo.
So, the current Yang Palace
is impenetrable.
We can't even enter the palace.
How could we save Princess?
Since we can't enter the palace,
we'll force them
to hand her over then.
Fourth Prince,
according to our current speed,
we can reach the Capital
within half a day.
Fourth Prince?
What did you say?
Fourth Prince, if you're tired,
we should take a break
at the stop in front of us.
We can continue tomorrow.
I'm not tired.
I was just wondering why
Father
didn't let us stay
and attack the Taibao Battalion.
Instead, he wants us
to return to the palace.
I don't know what His Majesty
is planning as well.
But I'm sure
His Majesty has his own concerns.
Do you think Father is doing this
because he thinks that
I will spoil his plan?
If that's the case,
why would His Majesty
ask you to do a reconnaissance
of the Taibao Battalion
in the first place?
Your Highness,
you're overthinking things.
Cousin, you're right.
But this time, I've helped Father
to complete a mission.
Say, do you think
Third Brother will
see me in a different light?